I am Raj Sharma I have one daughter and
I I had one son I loved him so much
Maggert very daughter cope with mando
husky mother co-producer kuru tamerica
cable a cup of acumen as a captive oh
I'm goo Sakura we are put that before me
409 he was a patch-up person subtly a
batch of cassava rose Katara Siddharth
tyrannically office in Allah or or cross
carry raha suddenly a Gauri I was
Escobar's Bochum even a bonfire
[Music]
he's missin absolute boot sector
Sirocco Papa PT Shadwick ellika I lost
my 32 year old old me son in an drunk
and drive road accident
if you don't mind can I ask you a Kirby
Capra grant actually however you going
back
[Music]
normally to major level
we I am very glad that you took this
decision to allow me to drive you home
safely
it's nepotism
mace liya karo tacky case you're capable
genican operate domain
[Music]